http://www.collectify.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy governs Collectify LLC's ("Collectify") treatment of personally identifiable information that Collectify collects when you use its Collectifycloud.com website ("Collectifycloud.com"). This Privacy Policy also covers Collectify's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Collectify's business partners share with Collectify. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Collectify does not own or control, or to people that Collectify does not employ or manage.By using Collectify.com, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy.This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 20, 2014. In the event that Collectify changes this Privacy Policy, Collectify will post notice of the change prominently on Collectifycloud.com. In addition, if you have registered on Collectifycloud.com, Collectify will contact you via email to notify you about the changes.Information Collection PracticesInformation Collectify Collects:Information You Provide: Collectify collects information that identifies you personally when you register on Collectifycloud.com, when you purchase Collectify software online, and when you use certain Collectify products or services. Collectify may also receive information that identifies you personally from its business partners.When you register online, you share your email address and password.When you use the services provided on Collectifycloud.com, you share all information that you input.When you order Collectify software online, you share your name, email address, telephone number, billing address, delivery address, credit/charge card number and credit/charge card expiration date.Information Collectify Automatically Receives: Collectify automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the pages on the website you visited.Cookies: A "cookie" is a small piece of information that a web browser can store temporarily on your hard drive. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, unless you change your browser settings to prevent it from accepting them.Collectify Cookies: Collectify may set and access Collectifycloud.com cookies on your computer. These cookies may contain some of the personal information you have provided to Collectify.Third Party Cookies: Collectify may also allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on Collectifycloud.com to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies are subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Collectifycloud.com's cookies.No Other Information: Collectify does not collect any information from you, other than stated above. Collectify only uses information it collects about you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. Collectify will not use your information in any other way without first obtaining your consent.Use of This Website By Children: Collectify does not knowingly solicit information from children under 13, nor does it knowingly market to children under 13. If you are a child under 13, please do not use Collectifycloud.com. If you are a parent of a child under the age of 13, and your child has used Collectifycloud.com, you may contact Collectify at privacy@collectify.com, and Collectify will delete any personally identifiable information about your child as soon as reasonably possible.Information Use, Sharing, And DisclosureInformation Collectify Uses: Collectify may use the information it collects to notify you about changes to Collectifycloud.com, software updates, and special offers Collectify thinks that you will find valuable.Information Collectify Shares:Service Providers: Collectify employs third party service providers to perform certain functions on its behalf. These service providers will have access to your personal information only to the degree it is necessary to provide the product or service you have requested. In addition, Collectify will require all service providers to afford the same level of privacy protection as required by this Privacy Policy.Collectify shares your name, billing address, credit/charge card number and credit/charge card expiration date with the service providers that process Collectify's credit/charge card orders.Collectify shares your delivery address and phone number with the facilities that fulfill orders, and the couriers that ship and deliver the software.Collectify may share your email address with service providers that manage the email messages Collectify sends to Collectifycloud.com users.Collectify may share your personal information with a service provider that provides customer service for Collectify.Sale of Information: Collectify does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others without your permission. You may opt-in to allow Collectify to share or disclose your information to third parties when your register. You may change your preferences by sending an email message to privacy@collectify.com.Aggregate Statistics: Collectify may provide aggregate statistics about its customers, sales, website traffic patterns, and related website information to reputable third parties. This aggregate information will not include any information that personally identifies you.Legal Reasons: Collectify will share your personal information, if required to do so by subpoena, court order, or other legal processes. Collectify may share your personal information if it finds that your actions on Collectifycloud.com violate the Terms and Conditions or any of its other usage guidelines for specific products or services.Information Accuracy, Reliability and SecurityChecking And Correcting Your Information:Checking Information: If you wish to know what information Collectify has collected about you, and how Collectify has used this information, please email Collectify at privacy@collectify.com.Correcting Information: Collectify gives you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time by sending an email message to privacy@collectify.com.Deleting Information: You may request deletion of your Collectifycloud.com account or any other information Collectify has collected about you by sending an email message to privacy@collectify.com.Reliability, Security and Integrity of Data:Reliability: Collectify promises to keep the data it collects about you accurate and reliable. Collectify will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent data it collects about you from being misused in any way.Security: Collectify protects your account information with your password. In certain areas, Collectify uses industry-standard secure socket layer ("SSL") encryption to protect data transmissions to Collectifycloud.com.Integrity: Collectify uses commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and current.Contacting CollectifyPrivacy Officer: Franklin Silverstone is the privacy compliance officer of Collectify. The privacy compliance officer is responsible for monitoring Collectify's compliance with this Privacy Policy. Franklin Silverstone can be reached via the contact information below.Contact Information: If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact Collectify by any of the means listed below:Email: privacy@collectify.com.Postal Mail: 18 Burr Street, Easton, CT 06612Compliance with Laws and EnforcementCompliance: Collectify has used its best efforts to comply with all applicable laws.Canada: This Privacy Policy complies with the requirements of the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act and the Quebec Act Respecting The Protection of Personal Information In The Private Sector.United States: This Privacy Policy complies with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").Enforcement: If you believe that Collectify has violated this Privacy Policy or is violating any laws, or you wish to make a complaint about Collectify's use of your information, you may contact any of the government agencies listed below.Canada:Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada: You may contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada by mail at 112 Kent Street, Ottawa, Ontario, K1A 1H3, or by telephone at 1-800-282-1376. In addition, you may visit the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada's website at http://www.privcom.gc.ca.La Commission d'accès à l'information du Québec: You may contact La Commission by mail at 575, rue St. Amable, Bureau 1.10, Québec, Québec, G1R 2G4, or by telephone at 1-418-528-7741. In addition, you may visit La Commission's website at http://www.cai.gouv.qc.ca.United States:Federal Trade Commission (the "FTC"): You may file a complaint with the FTC by visiting its website at http://www.ftc.gov.International Trade Administration (the "ITA"): You may contact the ITA by visiting its website at http://www.ita.doc.gov, or by telephone at 1-800-USA-TRADE.Internet Fraud Complaint Center (the "IFCC"): The IFCC is a partnership between the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the National White Collar Crime Center. The IFCC's mission is to address fraud committed over the Internet. You may file a complaint with the IFCC by visiting its website at http://www.ifccfbi.gov.New York State Attorney General: You may file a complaint with the New York State Office of The Attorney General Internet Bureau by visiting the bureau's website at http://www.oag.state.ny.us/internet_complaint/.Dispute Resolution: In the event you have a dispute with Collectify regarding this Privacy Policy, or Collectify's use of your personal information, Collectify will cooperate with data protection authorities located in Europe, as well as the enforcement agencies listed above.Updated: November 25, 2019
